https://www.bonvalecreations.com.au/privacy-policy

Contact Us
HomeEssential OilsEssential Oil BlendsSolubiliserBottles & AccessoriesRoller BallsBanksia Aroma PodsMicrowavable Soft ToysHeat PacksCreams & LotionsJewelleryRoom Sprays Essential Oil Storage BoxesUltrasonic DiffusersElectric Oil VaporizersElectric Oil BurnersNatural Handmade SoapsMetaphysicalCar ScenterOil BurnersElectric Wax Melt WarmerWax Melts or TartsDiffusersCandles and Tea LightsMassage/Carrier OilsGiftwareBooksFAQAbout us
Account
Home
PRIVACY POLICY
Privacy Policy
Please note that nowhere on our website do we retain any information regarding our customer credit card details ever.
Bonvale Creations is committed to the new Australian privacy legislation in the way it collects, uses, secures and discloses personal information. The Commonwealth Privacy Act 1988 requires companies to comply with the National Privacy Principles (NPPs). This document describes Bonvale Creations Privacy Policy.
The information we collect
We lawfully collect personal information that is necessary for our business to function. The information we collect and hold will depend upon the products and services you request from us and may include: • Information you provide us when you purchase goods or services. This information will include your name, address and contact details. . • Information derived from communications between us and you. We also collect information about you when you download trials from our website
www.bonvalecreations.com.au
The use of the facilities and services available through our website will determine the amount and type of information we collect. The only personal information we collect when you use our website is what you tell us about yourself, for example, by completing an online form when you request product information, or when you send us an email, we will record your mail address.
How we use your information We use the information we collect for the purpose disclosed at the time of collection or otherwise as set out in this Privacy Statement. We will not use your personal information for any other purpose without first seeking your consent, unless authorized or required by law. Generally we will only use and disclose your personal information: • To establish and maintain your relationship as a customer of Bonvale Creations. • To provide the products and services you have requested from Bonvale Creations. • To administer and manage those products and services. • To answer your inquiry. • For direct marketing by email, specials on products or services you have shown interest in. If we contact you in this way without obtaining your prior consent, we will provide you with the opportunity to decline any further marketing communications. If you at any time receive any communication from Bonvale Creations which you would not like to receive, please contact us and we will remove your name from our mailing list.
Access to your personal information
In most cases, you can gain access to the personal information that Bonvale Creations holds about you, subject to some exceptions allowed by law. If you would like to check or amend your contact details, please contact us. We will deal with all requests for access to personal information as quickly as possible.
Security
Bonvale Creations will take reasonable steps to keep secure any personal information which we hold and to keep this information accurate and up to date. Personal information is stored in a secure server or secure files. The Internet is not always a secure method of transmitting information. Accordingly, Bonvale Creations cannot accept responsibility for the security of information you send to, or receive from us over the Internet or for any unauthorized access or use of that information.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
It may be necessary for us to review and revise our Privacy Policy from time to time. An amended version will be posted on our website at www.bonvalecreations.com.au We suggest that you visit our website regularly to keep up to date with any changes.
Contact Us
If you would like any further information, or have any queries, problems or complaints in relation to this Privacy Policy or our information handling practices in general, please contact us via the contact form
CONTACT FORM
Copyright © 2014 to Present All Rights Reserved Bonvale Creations.
